<resources>
    <string name="app_name">3i Summit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">3i Summit</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Feed">Feedback</string>
    <string name="title_activity_testimonials">Testimonials</string>

    //UI Strings
    <string name="welcome_pic">naruto</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="mail">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="register_image">naruto</string>


    //Alumni Strings

    //agenda

    <string name="icem">Indira College of Engineering and Management</string>

    //aboutUS Data
    <string name="aboutus">Shree Chanakya Education Society’s “Indira Group of Institutes”, Pune was established in 1994, with the explicit vision to provide sustainable impetus to the corporate and entrepreneurial abilities in the youth.

The realization that a robust framework of education is indispensable for the growth of global leaders, the visionary, Dr. Tarita Shankar, Chairperson, Indira Group, integrated her pursuit of excellence and articulated educational institutions, known as Indira Group of Institutes (IGI), which imbibe human excellence and demonstrate strong social values, with a single minded pursuit of developing the youth to become business leaders.</string>


    <string name="about_indira">Indira College of Engineering and Management, established in 2007, is a venture of SCES. The institute is approved by All India Council of Technical Education (AICTE), New Delhi and Govt. of Maharashtra and affiliated to the University of Pune.
The post globalization era in India has resulted in fast pace development activities, shaping mighty economic developments. Infrastructure developments are meeting the industrial needs and making India a promising destination. This has created a need for professionals with expertise in multiple disciplines to spearhead the growth momentum. Engineering is an instrumental branch that will define the future course of these lofty development plans.
    At Indira College of Engineering and Management, we are committed to nurture the required expertise under one roof by creating competent and motivated technocrats and managers of tomorrow, who will use their technical knowledge and managerial qualities to
confidently and successfully lead the organization.
    </string>


    <string name="about3i">IGI started the Indira International Innovation Summit in 2008 with an aim to promote the Industry – academia linkages to enable the Indira College of Engineering and Management (ICEM), Pune to emerge as a Leading technical manpower source, but today this summit has become a platform for rekindling the power of creativity and innovations which would drive future innovation in the Industry.
There are immense opportunities in India for business growth in a growing economy, but it requires innovative minds to capture this market. Indira College of Engineering and Management organizes “Indira International Innovation Summit” and “HR Excellence awards” every year. The Innovators, Entrepreneurs and Senior leaders from companies of repute are recognized and awarded for their contribution in their respective fields and inspiring the spirit of innovative thinking.
</string>
</resources>
